shortlyst.com 2018-12-24

# Shortlyst Privacy Policy

Welcome to Shopalyst Inc ("Company," "we," or "us"). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our product discovery and shopping services ("Service"), and your choices about the collection and use of your information. By visiting our Website and/or using our services on our partner network, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use.

 **Information Collection and Use**

We collect the following types of information about you:

 _Information you provide us directly:_ We ask for certain information such as your username, first and last name, and e-mail address when you register for our Service. We may also collect and retain any information you provide in User Content you post to the Service. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.

 _Information we may receive from our partners and third parties :_ We may receive information about you from our partner sites where you use our Service, or third parties. For example, if you access our websites or Service through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by "following," "liking," adding the Company application, linking your account to the Service, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to Company. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. If you allow us access to your friends list, your friendsâ€™ user IDs, and your connection to those friends, may be used and stored to make your experience more social, and to allow you to invite your friends to use our Service as well as provide you with updates if and when your friends join Company. We encourage you to review and adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Company Service. You may also unlink your third party account from the Service by adjusting your settings on the third party service. If you unlink your third party account, we will remove the information collected about you in connection with that service.

 _Analytics_ : We collect and use analytics information (directly or via third party tools) that helps us improve the Service. This data is used in aggregate form such that it cannot identify any particular individual user.

 _Cookies_ : When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Company deliver you a better experience. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Service over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser, and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. You can use your browser settings disable or refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some features of the Service may not function as designed if cookies is disabled.

 _Logs_   : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile device each time you access the Service. When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

 **Sharing of your Information**

We will not rent or sell your information into third parties outside Company and its group companies (including any parent, subsidiaries and affiliates) without your consent, except as noted below:

We may provide limited access to your information with our business partners (publishers and retailers) for the purpose of providing the Service to you.

Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings.  

If the Company or substantially all of our assets are acquired, or in the course of a corporate divestiture, we expect that Your information such as customer names and email addresses, User Content and other user information related to the Service may be among the items would be transferred along with the other business assets.

To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose your information when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing the such Information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users or others.

We may share certain service type information, including information obtained through tools such as cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.): (i) with our third-party business partners for the purposes described in the section above on "Information Collection and Use."  

 **Protection of your Information**

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Company or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Company may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Company or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

The security of your information is paramount, and we use commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. While we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your account, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Company is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify users whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

 **Privacy of Children  **

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users.  If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will delete that information from our databases.

 **Links to other sites and services  **

Our Service may contain links to third-party websites. We have no control over the practices or the content of any of our partner companies, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third-party access to you User Content you do so at your own risk.  

 **Changes to this policy**

Company may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the â€˜last modifiedâ€™ date at the bottom of this page.

 **How to contact us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at [support@shopalyst.com](mailto:support@shopalyst.com)

This privacy policy was last modified on Nov 25th 2014.
